<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nRF5dev</title>
    <link>https://nrf5dev.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on nRF5dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{year}, All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2020 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://nrf5dev.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Getting started</title>
        <link>https://nrf5dev.com/tutorials/getting-started/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 13:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://nrf5dev.com/tutorials/getting-started/</guid>
        <description>In this Tutorial I will walk you throught all the necessary steps that you need to follow, in order to get started with the nRF5 development.
Step1: Get a Development Kit In order to run/test your applications, you need to have a development kit. the dev-kit consists of a development board, where your targeted SOC (system on chip) is soldered to with all the necessary components needed for its proper working.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Blinky Test</title>
        <link>https://nrf5dev.com/tutorials/test-blinky-app/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://nrf5dev.com/tutorials/test-blinky-app/</guid>
        <description>After getting your development kit and installing all the necessary software tools, this should be the time to run/test some examples from the nRF5_SDK. I will be using the blinky example under the peripheral examples folder.
Open the blinky project with SES IDE: I have extracted the nRF5_SDK .Zip file in C:\nRF\nRF5_SDK\v17.0.0\, so the blinky example folder location will be in C:\nRF\nRF5_SDK\v17.0.0\examples\peripheral\blinky.
In this folder you will have 2 options:</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Buttons and leds</title>
        <link>https://nrf5dev.com/tutorials/buttons-and-leds/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2020 13:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://nrf5dev.com/tutorials/buttons-and-leds/</guid>
        <description>Your nRF52 development kit already comes with 4 user-programmable buttons and 4 leds built in.
In this tutorial we&amp;rsquo;ll be looking into how to read these buttons states and control the leds. This should give you a better understanding on how to read and control pins states.
Getting started: For building the testing code, we&amp;rsquo;ll be starting with the blinky project located under the peripheral examples.
i&amp;rsquo;m using the nRF52840-DK (PCA10056), so i&amp;rsquo;ll launch the EM PROJECT FILE in .</description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>